[
    {
        "title": "Song Acronym Round"
    },
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "O _ _ _ _ - S _ _ _  C _ _ _ _ _  Y _ _ _  H _ _ _ _  O _ _",
        "answer": "Oasis - Stop Crying Your Heart Out"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "N _ _ _ _ _ _ - S _ _ _ _ _  L _ _ _  T _ _ _  S _ _ _ _ _",
        "answer": "Nirvana - Smells Like Teen Spirit"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "A _ _ _ _ - R _ _ _ _ _ _  I _  T _ _  D _ _ _",
        "answer": "Adele - Rolling in the Deep"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "G _ _ _ _ _  M _ _ _ _ _ _ - C _ _ _ _ _ _ _  W _ _ _ _ _ _ ",
        "answer": "George Michael - Careless Whisper"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "E _ _ _ _  J _ _ _  - C _ _ _ _ _  I _  T _ _  W _ _ _",
        "answer": "Elton John - Candle in the Wind"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "D _ _ _ _  B _ _ _ _ - H _ _ _ _ _",
        "answer": "David Bowie -  Heroes"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "B _ _ _ - S _ _ _ 2",
        "answer": "Blur - Song 2"
    },

    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "E _ _ _ _ _ _ _  L _ _ _ _  O _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ - M _  B _ _ _  S _ _",
        "answer": "Electric Light Orchestra - Mr Blue Sky "
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "S _ _ _ _  G _ _ _ _ - W _ _ _ _ _ _",
        "answer": "Spice Girls - Wannabe"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "T _ _  B _ _ _ _ _ _ - L _ _  I _  B _",
        "answer": "The Beatles- Let it be"
    }
]
